citifinancial.com 2008-05-24

# Internet Privacy Policy

|    
INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY   

We want you to understand what personal information about you is collected through this Web site.

We collect information you provide through an online loan application at this site when you submit the completed application. The information in your online loan application includes but is not limited to, your name, address, Social Security number, telephone number, e-mail address, income and occupation.

You can visit this site and find out about our products and services or use other value-added services without giving us any personal information about you.

If you are a customer, details about the personal information about you we collect and how it may be disclosed is contained in our Privacy Notice.

In order to provide better service, we may use "cookies" which may be set by another company for us. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site stores on your Web browser that can later be retrieved and read only by the same site. We use cookies for administrative purposes and to enhance your online experience. For example, we may use cookies to track the number of visitors to our site or to enable us to present rotating information to you at our site. You can set up your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. See more about cookies and online security for more information about this site.

When you click on a link contained on this site, you may leave this site and go to another Web site maintained by Citigroup, one or more affiliates or divisions of Citigroup, or possibly a non-affiliated third party. Linked sites maintained by Citigroup, or one or more of its affiliates or divisions, may have their own cookie policies. Linked sites maintained by non-affiliated third parties may have a cookie policy different from that of Citigroup and/or its affiliates.

Additionally, non-customers who receive a promotional email message about our products and services may elect to not receive further promotional email messages in accordance with the instructions we provide in the promotional email message. If you elect not to receive these messages, we will retain your e-mail address solely for the purposes of facilitating your request.

Information that you provide to us online, and in your online loan application, may be accessed and changed by contacting us. To protect your privacy, proof of identity or other authentication is required. To contact us, see [Contact Us](http://www.citifinancial.com/topnavigation/contactus.php).

From time to time, we may change this Internet Privacy Policy. The effective date of this policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy.

This policy was last modified 7/15/2007.

Our Privacy Notice  

Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you.

**_You Have Choices_** : As a CitiFinancial* customer, you have the opportunity to make choices about how personal information about you may be shared. As you consider this, we encourage you to make choices that enable us to provide you with quality products and services that help you meet your financial needs and objectives.

**_Security of Personal Information_** : The security of personal information about you is our priority. We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.

**_About This Notice_** : This notice tells you how we collect, handle, and disclose personal information about you. If you want to limit our disclosing this information, please see the **Privacy Choices Form** at the end of this notice. If you are a joint accountholder, we will accept instructions from either of you and apply them to the entire account. This notice applies to both current and former customers.

We may change this notice from time to time. If we do, we will notify you as required by applicable law.

**_Personal Information We Collect And May Disclose_** : The personal information we may collect about you comes from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you, such as your name, address, and telephone number,

  * Information about your transactions, such as your account balances, payment history and account activity, and

  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies and other sources, such as your credit bureau reports and other information relating to your creditworthiness.

We may disclose any of the above information that we collect to affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties as described below.

The term "personal information", as used in this notice, means information that identifies you personally. We may use information which does not personally identify you to help manage our businesses and to provide us, our affiliates, and other companies insight into consumer spending behavior. We may do this even if you ask us to limit disclosure of personal information about you, as described in the **Privacy Choices Form**.

**_Affiliates To Whom We May Disclose Personal Information_** : Our affiliates are the family of companies controlled by Citigroup. Affiliates to whom we may disclose personal information about you are in several different businesses, including banking, credit cards, consumer finance, securities and insurance. Our affiliates include those doing business under the names Citi Assurance Services, Citibank, CitiFinancial Retail Services, CitiMortgage, Primerica, and Smith Barney.

**_Nonaffiliated Third Parties To Whom We May Disclose Personal Information_** : Nonaffiliated third parties are those not part of the family of companies controlled by Citigroup. We may disclose personal information about you to the following types of nonaffiliated third parties:

  * Financial services providers, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, securities and insurance, and

  * Non-financial companies, such as companies engaged in direct marketing and the selling of consumer products and services.

If you fill in **Box 1** on the **Privacy Choices Form** , we will not disclose personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties except as follows. First, we may disclose personal information about you as described above in "Personal Information We Collect And May Disclose" to third parties that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. Second, we may disclose personal information about you to third parties as permitted by law, such as disclosures necessary to process and service your account, to protect against fraud and to protect the security or confidentiality of our records.

**_Your Privacy Choices:_ This section describes your privacy choices. Please remember that we will continue to protect your personal information regardless of your privacy choices.**

**_Disclosing to Nonaffiliated Third Parties (Box 1)_** : As described in this notice, we will limit the personal information about you that we disclose to nonaffiliated third parties if you fill in **Box 1** on the **Privacy Choices Form**.

**_Sharing With Citigroup Affiliates (Box 2)_** : Our ability to share information with our affiliates helps us to more easily provide you with quality products and services to meet your financial needs and goals.

The law allows us to share with our affiliates any information about our transactions or experiences with you. Unless otherwise permitted by law, we will not share with our affiliates other information that you provide to us or that we obtain from third parties (for instance, credit bureaus) if you fill in **Box 2** on the **Privacy Choices Form**.

**_Information for California Customers_** : In response to a California law, we will automatically treat accounts with California mailing addresses as if you filled in **Box 1** on the **Privacy Choices Form** and will not disclose personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties except as permitted by the applicable California law. We will also limit the sharing of personal information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us. To further restrict sharing with affiliates as described in this notice, you can fill in **Box 2** on the **Privacy Choices Form**.

**_Information for Vermont Customers_** : In response to a Vermont regulation, we will automatically treat accounts with Vermont mailing addresses as if you filled in **Box 1** and **Box 2** on the **Privacy Choices Form**. If we disclose personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we will only disclose your name, address, other contact information and information about our transactions or experiences with you.

                                                                        *****

Please allow approximately 30 days from our receipt of your privacy choices for them to become effective.

If you are also a customer of other Citigroup affiliates and you receive notice of their intent to share certain information about you, you will need to separately notify them if you do not want them to share such information.

                                                                        *****

**_Texas Consumer Privacy Notice_** : CitiFinancial is licensed and examined under the laws of the State of Texas and by state law is subject to regulatory oversight by the Office of Consumer Credit Commissioner. Any consumer wishing to file a complaint against CitiFinancial should contact the Office of Consumer Credit Commissioner through one of the means indicated below:

In person or U.S. Mail:  
2601 North Lamar Boulevard  
Austin, TX 78705-4207  
Telephone: (800) 538-1579  
Fax Number: (512) 936-7610  
E-mail: consumer.complaints@occc.state.tx.us  
**Website: www.occc.state.tx.us**  

*All references to CitiFinancial refer to the subsidiary of CitiFinancial Credit Company which is maintaining your account. These subsidiaries include: CitiFinancial Company, CitiFinancial Consumer Services, CitiFinancial Consumer Services, Inc., CitiFinancial Corporation, CitiFinancial Corporation, LLC, CitiFinancial, Inc., CitiFinancial of Virginia, Inc., and CitiFinancial Services, Inc.

CITIFINANCIAL is a registered service mark of Citigroup Inc.

                                                         Original (Customer)  
\----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  
             FILL IN PRIVACY CHOICES FORM BELOW, DETACH, AND RETURN

**_PRIVACY CHOICES FORM_** : If you want to limit disclosures of personal information about you as described in this notice, just fill in the appropriate box or boxes to indicate your privacy choices and provide all of the requested information. Then, send this form to the address listed below. Be sure to include account numbers since your privacy choices will be applied only to accounts listed.

_Box_

☐  1.  Limit the personal information about me that you disclose to nonaffiliated third parties.  
☐  2.  Limit the personal information about me that you share with Citigroup affiliates.

Please provide all of the requested information so that CitiFinancial can correctly administer your request.

My CitiFinancial account number(s) (list each account):  
(15 digits beginning with 67)

6 7 __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __

6 7 __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __ __

Name: ____________________________________________________

Address: __________________________________________________

City, State: ________________________________________________

Zip: _____________________________________________________

If you filled in any of the boxes above, please mail this form in a stamped envelope to:

**Privacy Choices  
CitiFinancial   
300 St. Paul Place BSP13A  
Baltimore, MD 21202  
**

|
